Guide to the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection TAM 527
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Organizational Printed Ephemera, 1938-2006
  - Communist Party of Kampuchea, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Communist Party of the Philippines, 1968, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Communist Party of the USA, 1946, 1962-1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Communist Party of the USA, 1969-1978 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Communist Party of the USA, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Communist Party of the USA: National Committee, 1944 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Communist Party of the USA: New York State, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Communist Party of the USA: Party Affairs, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Communist Party of the USA: Wisconsin, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Communist Party of Turkey Marxist-Leninist, undated (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Communist Party (London), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Communist Party USA (Marxist-Leninist) (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Communist Workers Movement, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Communist Youth Organization: In Struggle, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Community Bail Fund, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Community Media Project of Kitchener-Waterloo (Ireland), 1972 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - The Compass (Angola) (Boston, MA), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Concerned Blaw-Knox Workers, undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Concerned Citizens of Jersey City (interview in Grenada), circa 1983 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Concerned Parents and Students, undated (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Concerned Phone Workers, undated (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Concerned Union Members, undated (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Confederation of Iranian Students, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Congress of Afrikan People, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Cook County Hospital, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Counterattack (anti-communism), 1951-1964 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Counter-Attack (self-defense), undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - David Sibeko Memorial Committee (Chicago, IL), circa 1979 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - D. C. Native American Solidarity Committee (Washington DC), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Democratic People's Front for the Liberation of Palestine, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (New York, NY), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Democrats for the '80's (Washington DC), undated (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Derricke Brown/ Dan Johnson (police brutality), undated (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Disarm Now Action, undated (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Domhoff, William G: How to Commit Revolution in Corporate America, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Economic Histories (1970's NYC, depression - World War II), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Economics Summit Conference, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Essex Workers, undated (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - El Comite'/ Movimiento de Izquierda Nacional Puertorriqueno, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - El Salvador, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Elections 1980 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Emergency Land Fund, undated (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Farah Strike Support Committee, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Fascism, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - February First Movement (Washington DC), undated (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Federation of Revolutionary Socialists (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Fight Back (New York, NY), undated (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Fight, Don't Freeze, undated (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Fight for A Good Contract, undated (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Fight for Every Job Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Fight the Klan Defense Committee, undated (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Fight the Power, undated (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Fighting Times (Milwaukee, WI), undated (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Final Warning (Bronx, NY), undated (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Fliers (unidentified organization), undated (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1951-1958 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Languages Press, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Korea), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Languages Publishing House (Moscow), 1951 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Freedom Press (Frank Rizzo) (Philadelphia, PA), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Freedom Road Socialist Organization (Chicago, IL), 1987 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Gamma Publications (New York, NY), undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Georgia Communist League (Marxist-Leninist), 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Good Contract Committee, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - The Grapevine, 1977, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Grassroots Alliance ("Register Against Reagan"), 1980s (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Greater Yellow Springs Council of Anarcho-Drug Freaks, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Greensboro Collective, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Guardian (New York, NY), 1973, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Guerrilla Warfare, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Guerrilla Warfare: "Mini-Manual of the Urban Guerrilla", 1969 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Guevara, Che (Medical Cadre), undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Harper's Ferry Books (anti-Vietnam war), undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Hawaii Revolutionary Organization, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Haymarket Centennial, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Haymarket Collective, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Haywood, Harry (negro question), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Health Movement Organization (New York, NY), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Health Revolutionary Unity Movement, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Health Workers Council, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Hinton, William, undated (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - History of the Communist Movement: Paper/Draft, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Hitch Hiking: "On the Road Again", undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Homosexuality/ Gay Liberation, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Ignatin, Noel, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Illinois Coalition Against Reagan Economics (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - India: Communist Revolution I, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - India: Communist Revolution II, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - India: Communist Revolution III, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Indian Workers' Front, undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Indict Sgt. Lloyd For Murder, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Indochina Peace Campaign, 1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Indochina Peace Campaign: Bronx Chapter, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Ink Works (Ronnie Rat Show Comic Book) (Chicago, IL), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Institute for Labor Education and Research (New York, NY), 1980s (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Institute of Black Political Studies (Philadelphia, PA), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - International Conference for Solidarity With Kampuchea (Stockholm, Sweden), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - International Liberation School (self-defense), 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - International Marxist Group (London), 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - International Situation, 1980, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - International Socialists, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - International Women's Day Committee, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Iranian Students Association, 1971-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Ireland, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Irish Republican Information Service, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Italian Communist Party, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Jackson, George (Soledad Brothers), 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Jearl Wood Defense Committee (Harvey, IL), 1982 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Jefferson School of Social Science (New York, NY), undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - John Brown Education Project (Reseda, CA), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - John Brown Party (Tucson, AZ), undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - John Brown Society (Berkeley, CA), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - July 4th Coalition/ Rich Off Our Backs I, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - July 4th Coalition/ Rich Off Our Backs II, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Justice Graphics (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Kalamazoo Workers For Action (Kalamazoo, MI), undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Kampuchea Support Committee (New York, NY; Chicago, IL), 1979 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Kent Legal Defense Fund, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - King Jr, Martin Luther, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Komozi, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Labor Coalition on Public Utilities (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Labor Education and Research Project (Detroit, MI), 1980-1983 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Labor Institute (New York, NY), undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Labor Notes (Detroit, MI), 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Labor Task Force on El Salvador (CISPES), circa 1980 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Lakewood Nursing Home Union, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Lawrence and Wishart ("Democracy and the Class Struggle"), undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Lawyers for the People (Bakke Case) (New York, NY), undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - League for Proletarian Revolution (ML) (New York, NY), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - League for Proletarian Socialism, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - League for Revolutionary Struggle, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - League of Democratic Communists of Germany, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - League of Revolutionary Workers, circa 1971 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - League of Revolutionary Struggle (Oakland, CA), 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Liberated Guardian (New York, NY), undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Liberation Books, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Liberation Books, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Liberation Distributors, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Liberation Support Movement (Africa), 1974 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Liberator Press (Chicago, IL), 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Liberator Press (Chicago, IL), 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Linea Roja, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Lozand, Rudy, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Mahwah Fist (Ford Assembly Plant Workers in Mahwah, NJ), 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Male Stale News and Views, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Mao Tsetung: Three Worlds Theory, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Marxism-Leninism, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Marxist-Leninists (documents from first meeting of Nordic Marxist-Leninists), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - May 4th Coalition, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - May Day (various organizations), 1975-1980 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - May Day Blast, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - May Day Bookstore (Detroit, MI), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - May Day Committee, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Medical Committee For Human Rights, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Merit Publishers (New York, NY), 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Middle East Research Center (Israeli economy) (Buffalo, NY), undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Midwest Center for Labor Research, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Midwest Coalition Against Registration and the Draft (Kent State Anniversary) (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Militant Labor Forum, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Military Science/ Arming of the Masses, undated (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Milwaukee Solidarity, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miners Committee to Defend the Right to Strike, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Miners Right to Strike Committee (United Mine Workers of America), 1975-1978, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Mobilization Committee Against Police Brutality, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Modern Bookstore (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Moratorium-Attica Protest Committee (New York, NY), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Mothers Day Peace Walk, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Motor City Labor League (Detroit, MI), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Movement for a Democratic Society, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Mr. Coffee Organizing, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - National Abortion Rights Action League (NARAL), 1973-1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - National Black Counselors, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - National Black Lawyers Association, undated (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - National Black United Front, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - National Committee to Overturn the Bakke Decision, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - National Conference of Churches (Namibia) (New York, NY), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - National Conference on the Bakke Case, Affirmative Action and the Professions (New York, NY), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - National Council for Universal and Unconditional Amnesty, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - National Defense Committee, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - National Fight Back Organization (Chicago, IL), 1977 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - National Good Contract Committee, undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - National Health Insurance, undated (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - National Interim Committee for a Mass Party of the People (New York, NY), undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - National Labor and Law Center (Washington DC), undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - National May Day Committee, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - National Minority Caucus (NMC) (national question) (white chauvinism), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - National Network, Formation of MLS, undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - National Network of Progressive Health Advocacy Organizations, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - National Organization for Women, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - National United Workers Organization I, undated (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - National United Workers Organization II, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - National Workers Organization, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Near West Side People's Clinic, undated (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New American Movement, undated (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - New Century Publishers (CPUSA), 1946-1963 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New China Calendar, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New Directions Education and Research Foundation (Milwaukee, WI), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - New England Free Press I, undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - New England Free Press II, undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - New Left Education Project (Austin, TX), undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - New Left/ Student Movement, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - New Philadelphia Strike Fund, undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - New Outlook Publishers (CPUSA) I, 1965-1976 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - New Outlook Publishers (CPUSA) II, 1965-1976 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - New University Conference (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - New Voice, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - New York Communist Workers Organization, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - New York Metro Area Postal Union, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - New York Veterans Coalition, undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Nicaragua, undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - North American Congress on Latin America, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Northeast Ohio Committee to Defend the Miners, undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Northern California Anti-Imperialist Caucus, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - November 4th Coalition/ Committee, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Nuclear Freeze Referendum Committee (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - El Obrero, undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - October League I, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - October League II, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - October League III, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - October League: Cell Report, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - October League Speech, undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Ohio News Reel: Political Films (Cincinnati, OH), undated (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Ohio River Publications (fascism) (Cincinnati, OH), undated (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - On To Philly, undated (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - One Spark Music, undated (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Organization of Iranian People's Fedaee Guerrillas, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Organizing Committee for a New African Liberation Support Committee, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Organizing Committee for an Ideological Center, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Outline for a Party Programme, undated (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Pacific Studies Center (Palo Alto, CA), 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Palestine Communist Party, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Palestine National Liberation Movement, Fateh, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Pan-Africanist Congress of Azania (New York, NY), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - The Partisans, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Party of Labour of Albania, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Pathfinder Press (steel), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Peace Resource Center, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - People Against the Transit Hike, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - People Get Ready/ "Throw the Bum Out", 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission, Congressional Hearing on, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - People's Coalition Against Ford, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - People's College (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - People's College Press (Nashville, TN), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - People's Press (San Francisco, CA), 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The Pipeline, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Plain Dealer Picket, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Point Blank, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Police Brutality, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Police Repression, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Political Affairs (CPUSA), 1973-1977 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Popular Economics Press (Somerville, MA), 1973, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Position Paper: Content and Form in Poetry, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Position Paper: "Fight the Attacks on the Working Class: There Is a Way Out!", undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Position Paper: "Is There a 'Split' in the Ruling Class?", undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Position Paper: "On Discipline and Points of Attention", undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Position Paper: "The Significance of the New Deal: Fascism Is Here", undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Position Paper: Strategy and Tactics, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Position Paper: "United Front Against Monopoly Capitalism or United Front Against Fascism", undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Position Papers (from various unidentified sources), undated (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Postal Workers for a Good Contract, circa 1970s (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Postal Workers for the Advancement of Position Workers: Outlaw, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Prairie Fire (San Francisco, CA), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee (Attica), 1971 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Progress Publishers (Moscow) (Maoism), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Progressive Labor Party, 1966-1976 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Progressive Student Network, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Progressive University of Illinois at Chicago (CIA campus recruiting), undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Proletarian Cause, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Proletarian Center (Jersey City, NJ), undated (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Proletarian Unity League I, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Proletarian Unity League II, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Proletarian Unity League III, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Provisional Organizing Committee for a Marxist Leninist Party, 1958, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Puerto Rico, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Puerto Rican Revolutionary Workers Organization, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Puerto Rican Socialist Party, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Puerto Rican Solidarity Day Committee (New York, NY), undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Puerto Rican Student Union, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Radical America (CIO), circa 1971 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Radical Education Project, 1960s (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Radical Historians Newsletter, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Rainbow Terrace Rent Strike, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Rank and File Activism, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Red Detachment of Women, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Red Flag Publications (Kampuchea), 1978 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Red Prison Movement (George Jackson), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Re-Industrialization: Draft Article, undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Report: Capital Formation Progress Report, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Report: Milwaukee: Economic History and Characteristics, undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Report: Population of U.S. Cities, undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Report: "Social Context of the Latino Movement", undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Report: "Structure of the Monopoly Capitalist Ruling Class in the United States", undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Reports (from various unidentified sources), undated (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Resistencia Puertorriquena (New York, NY), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Resumes for Reagan, undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Revelationary Controversy Party, USA, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Revolution Books (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Revolutionary Action Movement, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Revolutionary Communist League (International) (New York, NY), undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - The (Revolutionary) Popular Front for the Liberation of Palestine, circa 1972 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade I, 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Revolutionary Students Brigade II, 1973-1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade: Seize The Times, 1974-1980 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Revolutionary Student Union, 1972-1973 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Revolutionary Workers Congress, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Revolutionary Workers League, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement (RYM), undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Right Idealism (elections), undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Rising Up Angry (political cartoons) (Chicago, IL), 1975 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Sacco and Vanzetti/ Bobby Seale and Ericka Huggins, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Salinas Citizens Committee in Defense of Farmworkers (Salinas, CA), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - San Francisco Womens' History Group, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Seacoast Area Workers' Committee: Unemployment Handbook (Dover, NH), undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Security, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Singer Strike (Singer Workers for a Good Contract), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Social Democrats USA (New York, NY), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Socialist Labor Party, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Socialist Workers Party, 1965-1972 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization, 1971-1976 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Sojourner Truth Organization, undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Solidarity Support Committee (Poland), undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Southern California Worker, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1971, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1967, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Soviet Union ("Notes and Impressions of USSR"), undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Soweto Brigade (Africa Liberation Day March), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - The Spark, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Spartacist (Communist Working Collective), undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Speech: "The Current Situation and the Role of Communists", circa 1980 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Srafprint Co-Op, undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Student Activism, undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Students for a Better Education, undated (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Students for a Decent Education, undated (Box 16, Folder 43)